{
  "questions": [
    {"question": "1- What is the output of console.log(typeof null)?",
    "correct_answer": "object",
    "answer1":"null",
    "answer2":"undefined",
    "answer3":"function"
  },
  {
    "question": "2- Which method is used to add one or more elements to the end of an array in JavaScript?",
    "correct_answer":"push",
    "answer1":"pop",
    "answer2":"shift",
    "answer3":"unshift"
  },
  {
    "question": "3- How do you create a new object in JavaScript?",
    "correct_answer":"let obj = {};",
    "answer1":"let obj = Object.create();",
    "answer2":"let obj = new Object[];",
    "answer3":"let obj = new[]"
  },
  {
    "question": "4- Which of the following is not a primitive data type in JavaScript?",
    "correct_answer":"array",
    "answer1":"boolean",
    "answer2":"number",
    "answer3":"string"
  },
  {
    "question": "5- How can you convert a string to a number in JavaScript?",
    "correct_answer":"Number('123')",
    "answer1":"Parse.Int('123')",
    "answer2":"parseString('123')",
    "answer3":"String.toNumber('123')"
  },
  {
    "question": "6- What is the output of console.log('5' + 2)?",
    "correct_answer":"52",
    "answer1":"7",
    "answer2":"NaN",
    "answer3":"undefined"
  },
  {
    "question": "7- Which keyword is used to declare a variable that cannot be reassigned?",
    "correct_answer":"const",
    "answer1":"let",
    "answer2":"var",
    "answer3":"static"
  },
  {
    "question": "8- What will the following code return: Boolean('false')?",
    "correct_answer":"true",
    "answer1":"false",
    "answer2":"null",
    "answer3":"undefined"
  },
  {
    "question": "9- Which of the following is the correct way to write an arrow function in JavaScript?",
    "correct_answer":"const add = (a, b) => a + b;",
    "answer1":"const add = (a, b) => { return a + b }",
    "answer2":"const add = (a, b) -> a + b;",
    "answer3":"const add = (a, b) -> { return a + b }"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 -How do you check if a variable x is an array in JavaScript?",
    "correct_answer":"Array.isArray(x)",
    "answer1":"x.isArray()",
    "answer2":"x instanceof Array",
    "answer3":"typeof x === 'array'"
  }
  ]
}